Blood Red is a western film directed by Peter Masterson.
Set in the Napa Valley in 1895, an immigrant family struggles
to keep their vineyards from industrialists.
Marco Collogero, played by Eric Roberts.
Sebastian Collogero, played by Giancarlo Giannini.
William Bradford Berrigan, played by Dennis Hopper.
Andrews, played by Burt Young.
Miss Jeffreys, played by Carlin Glynn.
Maria Collogero, played by Julia Roberts.
Blood Red is a 1989 American Western film directed by Peter Masterson and starring Eric
Roberts, Giancarlo Giannini, Burt Young, Lara Harris and Dennis Hopper.
Although it was filmed and completed in 1986, the film
was released three years later in 1989.
Part of the filming for Blood Red occurred at the Picchetti
Brothers Winery in Cupertino, California.